http://www.duvinage.com/privacy

Duvinage Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to Duvinage. This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal information we may collect, how we may use that information, and how we protect it. If you have any questions, please email us.
1. COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
You may provide personal information when you are in contact with Duvinage, for example by filling out a contact form. By providing personal information, you are allowing us to respond to any questions or requests you may have and to present products and services to you. If you are requesting a quote from a territory covered by an outside sales representative, your information may be shared with the respective sales representative in order to provide you with more localized customer service. When you place an order, your shipping information will be shared with the freight carrier. You will not be added to any Duvinage or third-party mailing lists. The types of personal information collected on our Site may include: name, address, phone number, email address, and IP address.
2. COLLECTION AND USE OF NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION
Duvinage may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. The types of non-personal information collected on our Site may include: referrer URL, approximate location, search queries, browser type, device type, and pages visited. This information is aggregated and used to help us provide more useful information to our customers and to understand which parts of our Site, products, and services are of most interest. Aggregated data is considered non personal information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.
3. COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES
The Site may use cookies and similar technologies for Site analytics, campaign analysis, and in order to offer you a more relevant experience. Such information is considered non personal information. IP addresses or similar identifiers may be considered personal information by local law. You may adjust your browser’s settings to control websites’ use of cookies.
4. COMMUNICATING WITH YOU
Duvinage or an authorized sales representative may call or email you with messages about your order or to respond to a request from you. Other types of communication may include: confirmation of receiving a request from you, confirmation of your purchase, and confirmation that your order has shipped. Once your order ships, the freight carrier will call or email you about your delivery or to respond to a request from you.
5. HOW WE PROTECT PERSONAL INFORMATION
We use technology safeguards, for example secure connections with data encryption for communication between the Site’s web servers and your client browser. We use organizational and physical safeguards as well to protect your information. If you have reason to believe your interaction with us is no longer secure, notify us immediately.
6. AUTHORIZED THIRD PARTIES
Third party services are employed on or in conjunction with the Site for secure payment processing, contact information, site optimization, social media integration, statistical analysis, marketing assistance, and providing customer service or support. These authorized third parties have agreed to use at least the same level of privacy protections and data handling policies described in this Privacy Policy and are permitted to use the information only for the purpose of performing these functions.
7. A NOTE TO PARENTS AND GUARDIANS
The Site is intended for customers, and is not directed at children under 13 years old. In accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, we do not knowingly collect information on children. If you are a parent or guardian with concerns that your child has provided information in a manner not permitted by law, please
email us to remove the data.
8. DATA RETENTION
Duvinage does not retain personal information longer than necessary. Duvinage will keep personal information while we have a relationship with you, for example as long as you are a customer (and for a reasonable period thereafter). Duvinage will store your personal information for as long as needed, or permitted, based on the reason why we obtained it (consistent with applicable law).
9. INFORMATION REQUESTS BY LEGAL AUTHORITIES
Duvinage reserves the right to disclose any information deemed necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. Duvinage also may disclose your information when applicable law requires or permits such disclosure, including exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection purposes. You acknowledge that Duvinage may preserve any transmittal or communication by you with Duvinage, and may also disclose such data if required to do so by law.
Updated by Duvinage LLC on August 29, 2020
Contact Us | Phone: (301) 733-8255 | Fax: (301) 791-7240
Made in the USA Since 1895.
Connect with us
© 2020 Duvinage LLC. All rights reserved.
